#### Contact

cpati001@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cristhian-patino-46166062 (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

BLS

Nursing

**Acute Care** 

# Languages

French (Elementary)

Italian (Elementary)

English (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

**PALS** 

**BLS** 

**CCRN** 

**ACLS** 

# Cristhian Patino

Travel CVICU Registered Nurse at Nicklaus Children's Health System

Naples, Florida Area

# Summary

Experienced Pediatric Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Pediatric Critical Care (CCRN), Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Acute Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Nursing Practice from The University of Texas at Arlington.

# Experience

Nicklaus Children's Health System Travel CVICU Registered Nurse November 2019 - April 2020 (6 months) Miami, Florida

#### Nemours

Travel CVICU Registered Nurse July 2019 - October 2019 (4 months)

Orlando, Florida

Children's Minnesota Travel Pediatric CVICU Registered Nurse January 2019 - July 2019 (7 months) Minneapolis, MN, United States

Travel Pediatric CVICU Registered Nurse at Children's Minnesota Hospital

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center Travel Pediatric Intensive Care Unit (PICU) Registered Nurse July 2018 - January 2019 (7 months)

New York, New York

Jackson Health System
Pediatric ICU and Transplant Registered Nurse

### August 2014 - December 2018 (4 years 5 months)

Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Pediatric ICU and Transplant Registered Nurse

## NYU Langone Health

Travel Pediatric Intensive Care Unit (PICU) Registered Nurse February 2018 - June 2018 (5 months)

New York, New York

Travel PICU RN at NYU Langone Health's Tisch Hospital

Miami Children's Health System Registered Nurse - Pediatric Intensive Care Unit (PICU) November 2013 - April 2018 (4 years 6 months)

Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Pediatric Intensive Care Unit Registered Nurse

Cleveland Clinic Registered Nurse December 2011 - November 2013 (2 years)

Float Pool LPN-RN

# Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing Practice · (2018)

Barron Collier High School (2003)

Florida International University